spare parts for an airplane are sold like that,
запчасти к самолётом так и продаются
you know, like this, to the market You come and
знаешь вот так на рынок Приезжаешь да
like grandma bought 2 kg of strawberry meat,
типа бабка купил 2 кг мяса клубники
in short, my wife asked me to buy that too Oh
короче жена попросила Да купить и ту О
[ __ ], I need another spare part for the airplane.
бля ещё запчасть к самолёту надо
comrade, I’m waiting for you to give him
ждёте где-то нет товарища жду вы его
a lift, well, we go to work together, I
подвозить ну на работу вместе ездим
just understood. And who do you work as a pilot, a
просто понял А кем работаете пилотом
pilot of what civil aviation? It’s cool
пилотом чего гражданской авиации
how things are now with civil
Прикольно как сейчас у вас с гражданской
aviation
авиацией
after the start of everything except Europe, not
после начала сво всё кроме Европы не
all the same, I mean on the technical
всё-таки я имею в виду по технической
side, from what I saw there  that these ava
части по что там я видел что эти ава
koro of Dubai are dragging dragging Yes, well, in short, well, it’s
коро Дубая таскают таскают Да ну короче
harder It’s already become because I saw
ну тяжелее Уже стало потому что я видел
that in the corn, in short, this one sat down Well, it was a long time ago, it
то в кукурузе сел короче один этот е Ну
would have been
это давно же было это е до этого бы то
in the corn for a long time before this This is recently where
что в кукурузе давно Вот это недавно где
he sat down for about six months  back somewhere in Siberia,
сел где-то полгода назад где-то в Сибири
too Well, there, yes, there
тоже А ну там да
can be all sorts of strange weather there. Yes,
там бывает бывает погода всякие такие
somehow they cut rubber, we
непонятные Да както рези резину у нас
make spare parts from No, well, the point is that
делают запчасти с Не ну Суть в том что
the frequency of these types of emergency
типа частота вот этих типа нештатных
situations has increased. I looked, I read
ситуаций выросла Я смотрел Читал
the analytics, but I can’t be exact  numbers yes
аналитику да я не могу точные цифры да
now to voice, but the frequency of emergency
сейчас озвучить но частота нештатных
situations is possible, perhaps the planes
ситуаций возможно возможно самолёты
are aging correctly, they are not Young
стареют же правильно они же не Молоде
and Well, it turns out that these sanctions
и Ну так получается что санкции эти
affect the flight sector Well, if you don’t
влияют на лётный сектор Ну если не
count the fact that they don’t supply new
считать то что не поставляют новых
planes, then
самолётов то
no. How not? Well, if the spare parts are the same
нет Как нет Ну так если же запчасти тоже
type  Is there service maintenance or not
типа обслуживание сервисное есть или нет
? Well, I’m talking about spare parts from Dubai, they carry
Ну я же говорю запчасти из Дубая таскают
spare parts and maintenance Well,
запчасти а обслуживание Ну
accordingly, maintenance for
соответственно обслуживание
this is for this,
за это
I won’t say exactly now, I don’t remember where, but
я сейчас точно не скажу не помню где но
somewhere they do it, I think they fly Vran or
где-то делают по-моему они Вран летают
something [ __ ], they are serviced the same way as
что ли бля обслуживаются так арара как у
yours  but if European or American
вас же если европейские или американские
companies are not Vira, it definitely doesn’t make a difference
компании не Вира точно не разница
God, it’s the same thing that I Naf
Господи это тоже самое что я Наф
will supply a [ __ ] non-original
поставлю бля не оригинальную
spare part Yes, but there is a difference if you
запчасть Да но есть разница если вы над
supply a non-original spare part and
поставите не оригинальную запчасть да и
you will have something rattling about it on
у вас что-то будет тарахтеть на это на
the move, that’s one thing right  Yes, if you
ходу это одно спра Да если вы на самот
put a non-original part on it, well, it
поставите не оригинальную часть Да ну
will fall with a lot of money. It’s just that, roughly
упадёт там со Сколь па Просто она грубо
speaking, it was not bought from an official dealer,
говоря куплена не у официального дилера
I can also buy it, go to the
я так же могу купить
market for some correct
поехать на рынок на какую-то правильно
spare parts, there are some there or in a store not
запчасти там какие-то или в магазине не
in the official one. Usually  Usually they sell spare parts for an
в официально Обычно Обычно у запчасти к
airplane, you know, like this,
самолётом так и продаются знаешь вот так
to the market. You come, like, grandma bought
на рынок Приезжаешь да типа бабка купил
2 kg of strawberry meat, in short, my wife asked me to
2 кг мяса клубники короче жена попросила
buy another spare part for the airplane, I need to take it
купить ещ запчасть к самол надо взять
to the rescue in my Ford, right now
сказа к приме в своём Форде сейчас же
all the official dealers have left,
ушли правильно все официальные дилеры
so I’m going to the market  there's a big one there.
так я еду на рынок там какой-то большой
We have a consular market. So
У нас вот консульский рынок есть Так
wait, don't look at Ford, don't look at the
подожди ты не смотри Ford ты не смотри
auto industry, don't
автопром ты не не
look up to what they're selling there. Listen, in
равняйсь что там торгует Слушай дай
short, damn, engines for an airplane, like
короче блин моторы к самолёту типа
you know the purchase, maybe someone will come in and ask for
знаешь закуп может кто-то зайдёт спросит
spare parts, yeah, what-  then
правда запчасти Да ну какие-то
critical spare parts Yes, there’s an
критические запчасти Да там фильтра
oil filter like this And how much experience do you already have,
масла типа такое А сколько у тебя уже
like a pilot, seven
стажа типа лётного семь
seven Cool It turns out you’ve
семь Прикольно Это получается ты с 22
been flying since you were 22
лет летаешь
No, of course not Well, now you’re
Нет ну как нет Ну тебе сейчас
229 33 I’m not 29
229 33 мне не 29
33 not It seems to me that you’re 29
33 не Мне кажется что тебе 29
understood Yes you  this is how long it takes you to
понял Да ты это со скольки получается с
fly
ше летаешь
Yes, and my friend, how long has he been
Да а друган сколько
flying? My friend just recently
летает Друган только недавно
graduated And what did
закончил А что
my Moscow Aviation graduate? Cool But
заканчивал мои Московский
look at what they
Прикольно А вот это смотри что вот нам
tell us When, for example,
рассказывают Когда например
they launched some kind of drone It seems that because of
запустили беспилотник какой-то Вроде да
this there is a Vnukov or Domodedov airfield there
из-за этого там аэродром Внукова там или
stopped the reception Well, they
Домодедова остановил приём Ну они же в
basically fly from there from the other side
основном оттуда летят с той стороны
correctly, I don’t mean for the airfield
правильно не я имею в виду для аэродрома
this is really critical Yes, no,
это действительно критически Да нет ну
just a tactic for safety, I understand, well,
просто тактика для безопасности понял ну
it doesn’t fly at the airport, there are turnips there
оно в аэропорту не долетает там репки
Well, if you look, if the airport
стоят Да ну если смотри если аэропорт
Stopped for an hour it  Well, what kind of losses
Остановился на час это ж Какие потери
or or Well, I understand Yes, well, they’ll just
или или Ну понят Да ну просто рейсы
reschedule the flights Yes, there are some kind of payments, Yeah, like, I understand
перенесут Да там выплаты какие-то
And Oleg, you didn’t try to
эти Угу типа понял А Олег ты не пробовал
go to the Military Aviation yes No, why not, well, I
в Военную авиацию идти да Нет зачем не
don’t know because many people
ну не знаю потому что многие типа
say that A And it’s the other way around after the
говорят что А И это наоборот после
military  are they going into civilian life or
военной в гражданку идут или нет Да не
not? Yes, no, no, well, there are some, well, damn, like
не Ну есть такие ну
200, there are 220,000 like, well, that’s
[__] типа за 200 там за 220.000 типа Ну
220 for a civilian or a
такое 220 это у гражданского или у
military man, but not for a military man, but for a Civilian,
военного а нет военный а Гражданский
how much, well, 400,500 turns out, so it
сколько ну 400 500 получается так
turns out that a Civilian Pilot
получается что Гражданский Пилот больше
earns more than a military Pilot Well, of course  And what’s the
получает чем военный Ну конечно А в чём
joke, how to understand what’s the joke and why
прикол как понять в чём прикол а зачем
then do they go to the military where someone
они тогда идут на военного где кто-то
learned to fly on fighter planes,
учился на истребителях летать на сушках
I don’t know on the ground that’s right, they
там я не знаю на гах правильно у них
don’t have access to a [ __ ] Boeing. Well,
нету допусков [__] к боингом
damn it, I’ve learned how much to study on a Boeing
Ну так блин отучилась сколько на Боинг
if
от учиться если
he’ll change his shoes for at least three years. Well,
он переобуться ну года три минимум Ну
who would go like a military man to change his shoes, especially
кто пойдёт типа военный переобуться тем
now it’s just damn, why are they
сейчас просто блин а что они тогда
even going then that they shouldn’t immediately go to
вообще иду что сразу не идти на
civilian life? Well, damn, someone was a military man,
гражданское Ну блин кто-то был военным
you know before all this started, it’s not like that. I’m
понимаешь до начала всего этого не так Я
not saying that now in  time s And in
не говорю что вот сейчас во время с А
general, before, well, why do they go then
вообще раньше ну зачем они тогда идут
if citizens, I think, are paid more by the military
если граждан думаю военно больше
? Well, maybe, maybe. Well, I
платят Ну может быть может быть Ну я
gave you an example. How much they pay there
тебе привёл пример Сколько платят там
now, I don’t know. Maybe they pay 250,
сейчас я не знаю Может им 250 платят
maybe they pay 300. But these courses like
может 300 платят А вот эти курсы типа
managing a Boeing are just like  in
управления боингом это прямо типа в
Russia, like, yes, we
России типа проходят такие Да у нас
have training simulators now, I understand. Well,
сейчас да тренажёры есть понял Ну а
now the sanctions simulators are still
сейчас санкции тренажёры всё равно типа
teaching, or like, well, the simulator, that is, the training device was
учат или как ну тренажёр то есть тренаж
not
не
taken away, and there is understood Yes, I
увезли
understand, maybe you have some questions
Да понял у тебя может какие-то вопросы
for me, and where are you from?  in general,
есть ко мне да так сам откуда вообще
the city of Khmelnitsky I said at the very beginning
город Хмельницкий Я же в самом начале
that something has already been hushed up, okay, let’s
назвал что-то уже замята хорошо давай
run away. Come on, let’s do
побегу Давай
something, he’s a man of
давай что-то он
few words, subscribe to Telegram
немногословный подпишись на Telegram
right away, but
прям зараз овин а
for now it’s even more and more important
пок це дуже и дуже важливо
L
L